lucybumarketing.com 2015-04-25

# Privacy Policy with LucyBuMarketing - Get Targeted Visitors to your website today

This privacy statement describes how Luckybumarketing.com collects and uses the personal information that you provide on our website : **LuckyBuMarketing.com**

It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

**We collect the following personal information from your:**

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address through our payment processor
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account id and password
  * Preferences Information such as order history and marketing preferences

We also collect the following information from you Information about your business such as company name, type of business, business goal

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

**We use this information to:**

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Send you a monthly and special offer newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Respond to your questions and comments
  * Conduct research and analysis

**Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us by filling out the form on the Contact Us page.

**Sharing of your Information**

At LucyBuMarketing.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Any information we collect, such as email addresses, is submitted at the visitor's will. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties

We may also disclose your personal information as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

if Luckybumarketing.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

**Cookies**

All browsers offer "cookies" and if you permit their use, they will store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to the site that placed the cookie. A cookie is a simple piece of text. It is not a program, or a plug-in. It cannot be used as a virus, and it cannot access your hard drive. Cookies simply assist in tracking which features you like best and allow content to be customized upon your return, according to prior preferences at that site. They gather and hold NO personal information.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of LucyBuMarketing.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

**At LucyBuMarketing.com, we may use cookies to:**

Save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites. We do not use cookies to identify, monitor or track any personally identifiable information. Our cookies in and of themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information about you. We do not merge or associate our cookie information with any personally identifiable information obtained by us or from third parties. You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. For more information on how to modify your browser settings to block or filter cookies, see <http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq/>. 

However, note that if you reject some or all cookies, your experience at our sites and on other sites throughout the World Wide Web may not be complete. Some sites require cookies to function, such as those with e-commerce features. In addition, if you do not allow cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of personalized content delivery offered by us or other Internet sites.

**Website Security**

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us by filling out the form on the Contact Us page. 

In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

**Contact Information**

You can contact us about this privacy statement by filling out the form on the Contact Us page.
